

Maciej Hnat

Senior Frontend Developer

Phone: +48 500 767 393 Email: maciekhnat@gmail.com

LinkedIn: /in/maciej-hnat/ GitHub: /mecies

Website: https://maciejhnat.netlify.app/

Senior Frontend Developer with 4 years of experience building engaging web applications using React and Vue. I specialize in creating user-friendly interfaces, optimizing website performance, and implementing responsive designs. My dedication to continuous learning and improvement ensures high-quality results that exceed client expectations. With leadership experience in managing and mentoring small frontend teams, I am committed to achieving project goals on time and on budget.

Skills

Technologies

React.js	Vue.js	Svelte	Angu	larJS	rJS TypeS		Next.js		Nuxt.js	Gats	by.js
HTML5	CSS3	JavaScrip	t ES6	React	Query	Apo	llo Grapl	nQL	Redux	SA	SS
Styled Con	Tailwind	d CSS Mater		al UI	Chakra UI		Storybook		Storyblok		
Jest Playwright Cypr		Cypres	ess Prettier		ESLint No		ode.js	js Ruby		Ruby on Rails	
Django	npm	Yarn L	erna	GraphQ	QL W	/ebSocI	kets	WebR	ТС	Prisma	
Firebase	Postgre	SQL M	ongoDB								

Languages

Polish native English full professional proficiency

Work experience

Senior Frontend Developer & Tech Lead

July 2021 - now

Swapcard

- Developing and maintaining an all-in-one platform for creating virtual events in a team of 15 frontend developers.
- Developing and maintaining a design system for the company.
- Developing a professional live streaming studio application from scratch as a single frontend developer.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.

- Working closely with the product and design teams to deliver the best user experience.
- Introducing new technologies, design patterns, and best practices to the team.
- Introducing frontend-centric e2e tests to the team preventing regression in SEO, a11y, and SSR.
- Leading a team of 4 developers.
- Mentoring and coaching junior developers.

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Styled Components, Storybook, Apollo GraphQL, GraphQL, WebSockets, WebRTC, Jest, Cypress, Playwright, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js, Yarn, Lerna

Senior Frontend Developer

May 2022 - now

Xfive · Part-time

- Developing a platform that eases the process of translating ancient buddhist text for the Laiden University.
- Maintaining a couple of small projects with on-demand work.
- Working closely with the client to deliver a tailor-made solution to their domain needs.
- Introducing new technologies and tools to the company.
- Leading a team of 2 frontend developers.

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, React Query, TypeScript, Styled Components, SASS, Jest, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js, Yarn

Frontend Developer

October 2020 - July 2021

Infermedica

- Developing an Al-powered medical diagnosis platform for doctors and patients.
- Developing and maintaining a design system for the company.
- Maintaining a legacy medical application and delivering it to the clients.
- Maintaining an existing marketing website and developing a new one with CMS from scratch.
- Working in a team of 10 frontend developers.
- Mentoring and supporting junior developers and newcomers.
- Customizing and integrating the platform for the needs of the client.

Technologies: Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Svelte, AngularJS, Django, TypeScript, JavaScript ES6, SASS, Storybook, Storyblok, Jest, ESLint, Prettier, npm

Junior Frontend Developer

February 2020 - October 2020

Monterail

• Developing a journey planner and online booking platform for European travel.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.

- Developing an online pharmacy platform for the US market.
- Developing an internal e-learning platform for the company.
- Developing an internal employee growth framework platform for the company.
- Working in multiple teams of 1-5 frontend developers on multiple projects.

Technologies: Vue.js, React.js, Next.js, Nuxt.js, Redux, TypeScript, SASS, Styled Components, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, Jest, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js, npm, Yarn

Frontend Developer Intern

November 2019 - February 2020

flashPub

- Developing a platform for creating and managing scientific micro publications.
- Working closely with the CEO and CTO of a startup.
- Working in a team of 2 frontend developers.
- Learning the basics of frontend development.

Technologies: React.js, TypeScript, Redux, Material UI, Styled Components, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js, Firebase, npm

Projects

Backstage app

July 2022 - now

Real-time live streaming studio web app

Article: https://release.swapcard.com/introducing-speaker-backstage-3yviJa

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Styled Components, Storybook, Jest, Apollo GraphQL, WebSockets, WebRTC, GraphQL, ESLint, Prettier

OPLU

May 2022 - March 2023

Web application for the Open Philology that eases the process of translating ancient texts.

Demo: https://staging.openphilology.eu/

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, React Query, Styled Components, Jest, ESLint, Prettier, Node.js

Event app

July 2021 - now

All in one event app for event attendees.

Demo: https://app.swapcard.com

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Styled Components, Storybook, Jest, Cypress, Playwright, Apollo GraphQL, GraphQL, Node.js, ESLint, Prettier, Lerna

Studio app

July 2021 - now

Studio app for event organizers.

Demo: https://studio.swapcard.com/

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Styled Components, Storybook, Jest, Apollo

GraphQL, GraphQL, ESLint, Prettier

Symptomate

October 2020 - July 2021

Web app and a registered Class I medical device in the European Union. Symptomate is a medical device regulated by the FDA as a general wellness product in the US.

Demo: https://symptomate.com/interview/0

GitHub: https://github.com/infermedica/component-library

Technologies: Vue.js, TypeScript, AngularJS, Django, SASS, Storybook, Jest, ESLint, Prettier

CodersCard

July 2020 - June 2021

CodersCard is a tool that helps developers to create a professional portfolio in minutes.

Demo: https://coders-card.netlify.app/

GitHub: https://github.com/CodersCrew/coders-card

Technologies: React.js, Gatsby.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Material UI, Storybook, GraphQL, ESLint,

Prettier

Montelearn

May 2020 - July 2020

An open-source platform for creating e-learning apps. While it doesn't solve the challenge of access to the Internet, it answers to the need of having low-cost, low resource-demanding solutions.

Article: https://www.monterail.com/blog/montelearn-open-source-platform-e-learning-apps

GitHub: https://github.com/monterail/montelearn

Technologies: React.js, Next.js, TypeScript, Tailwind CSS, Jest, ESLint, Prettier

NativeSpeaker

March 2019 - July 2019

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process.

NativeSpeaker is a platform that connects people who want to learn a language with native speakers who want to teach it.

Demo: https://nativespeaker.com.pl/

Technologies: HTML5, SASS, JavaScript ES6, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL

Education

Business Informatics

October 2017 - July 2020

Wroclaw University of Economics

Bachelor's degree. Specialization in system analysis and design.